Our next exercise, which is going to be a very short exercise,
我们的接下来要做的练习将会是一个很短的
is going to look at various ways of alerting users.
实现各种警告的练习
We have already seen that we have labels, badges, alerts and
我们已经看过诸如标签 徽章 警告
progress bars to inform the user.
以及进度条这些用来提示用户的东西是长啥样的
In this exercise, we're going to examine labels and badges.
在这个练习里面 我们将会去实现标签和徽章
Alerts will be explored further in the assignment that follows.
对于警告 我们将会在接下来的大作业里面实现
Progress bars are a bit difficult to illustrate at this moment
进度条对目前的学习进度而言有些难以阐述
because we don't have any dynamic behavior on our website yet.
因为我们的网页现在还没有任何动态的表现
That requires some server-side support.
而那是需要一些服务端的支持的
So we'll come back to examine progress bars
所以在接下来的某些课程中 我们会回过头来
in more detail in some of the later courses.
详细地讲进度条的知识
Getting back to our webpage, in the index.html page we see that we
回到我们的网页 在 index.html 里面
are displaying a dish on the page here.
我们可以看到我们在这显示了一道菜的信息
Now, I'm going to add a label and a badge to this dish name.
现在 我会在这道菜名字的旁边 加一个标签和一个徽章
Thereby, explore the use of labels and badges.
希望你们可以通过我的实现来学习到 如何使用标签和徽章
Moving to our HTML code.
进入 HTML 代码部分
Right next to the name of the dish, I'm going to add a label.
我将在这里这道菜的名字 Uthappizza 旁边加一个标签
So I have added the label using the span tag.
你可以看到我是用一个 span 标签来实现的
With the class label, label-danger and
我对其设置了 class="label label-danger label-xs"
label-xs with the letters Hot inside the span.
并将其内容设置成了 Hot
So this should display a label right next to the name
这么做了以后 这道菜的名字旁边 将会接一个标签
of the dish with Hot in there, in red color.
标签将会以红色为背景 以白色的 Hot 为内容
Going back to the webpage,
回到我们的网页
you can now notice that there is a label right next to the name of the dish.
你可以发现我刚刚说的都是真的
In the next step, I'm going to add a badge, right next to the label.
对于下一步 我们将会在这个标签右边 再加一个徽章
Here I am using the span with the class, badge.
我同样是用 span 来实现的 注意到我设置了 class="badge"
And then I am adding a price of the dish, right next to the label there.
然后我将这道菜的价格设置为了 这个徽章的内容
So you can see in the code how I have added the badge into place.
你可以仔细看看我是怎么写这段代码的
Now looking at the result of adding this you will notice on the website that
让我们看看结果 你可以看到现在我们的网页中
right next to the label you now have the price of the dish being displayed there.
那个 Hot 标签右边跟了一个显示价格的徽章
Now I have leveraged the badge class
事实上 用徽章来表示价格
in order to display the price of the dish here.
确实是一个常用且优雅的实现
Now the badge class is a lot more versatile than that.
当然 徽章能做的事有非常非常多
We'll explore more about using badges when we have dynamic behavior on our website.
当我们对我们的网页加入动态行为后 我们会 回过头来看看徽章更多的应用
This completes this exercise.
以上 我们完成了这次练习
In this short exercise we examined labels and badges.
在这个小练习里 我们学习了如何使用 标签和徽章
We'll look at alerts and progress bars later.
对于警告和进度条 我们以后会学习 【翻译 - Carefree0910】